One morning, Humf looked out of the window.
一个早晨  Humf看向窗外
Everything had white on it.
一切都被白雪淹没了
There were more little bit of white falling from the sky, too.
还有一些白雪从天空缓缓落下
Snow! It's snowing!
雪哎   下雪了
Let's all go to the park. Come on, Humf.
我们都去公园吧  来吧  Humf
You want to go play in the snow, don't you?
你不是就喜欢在雪里玩儿吗
Humf's mom and dad were very excited.
Humf的爸爸妈妈都很兴奋
Better dress warmly, Humf.
我们要穿暖和点哦  Humf
It's going to be cold in the snow.
雪里很冷的
What about breakfast?
早饭怎么办
We can have some breakfast when we come back.
我们回来的时候可以吃点早饭
Humf couldn't see his fingers now, just big red mittens!
Humf现在看不到他的手指了 只有红色的手套了
Is everybody ready?
每个人都准备好了吗
Yes.
是的